♪ ♪
♪ ME NO CONVERSATE WITH THE FAKE, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES INDEPENDENT BITCHES, THAT PART ♪
♪ I JUST WANT THE PAPER, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES FLAVORED ♪
♪ THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART ♪
♪ [POST-HOOK: SCHOOLBOY Q] AYY! THAT PART ♪
♪ BANG THIS SHIT IN THE HOOD ONE TIME ♪
♪ LIL BITCH I'M BACK AND POPPIN' ♪
♪ TELL THAT UGLY BITCH TO MOVE AWAY, I NEED MORE OPTIONS ♪
♪ BROKE? THEN FIX YOUR POCKETS, ALL I DO IS PROFIT ♪
♪ QUARTER MILLION, SWITCHIN' LANES... THAT PART ♪
♪ BET MY BITCH MOVE THE SAME OLD THING... THAT PART ♪
♪ 405 WITH THE GUN OFF SAFETY... THAT PART ♪
♪ A.M. STILL TRYNA MAKE THAT PLAY ♪
♪ RICH OR POOR, NIGGA, CHOOSE YOUR FATE ♪
♪ STYLE ON TOP OF STYLE, NIGGA ♪
♪ FIVE YEARS I'VE BEEN RICH, NIGGA ♪
♪ DROVE BEAMERS DOWN FIG, NIGGA ♪
♪ PUSHED PORSCHES DOWN BROADWAY ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN DIVIN' IN DIFFERENT HOES, NIGGA ♪
♪ GOT A CHAIN THAT'S WORTH THE ROLLS, NIGGA ♪
♪ GOT AN ENGINE BACK WITH THE TOP IN IT ♪
♪ NIGGA DRIVIN' IT LIKE IT'S A BOMB IN IT ♪
♪ ME NO CONVERSATE WITH THE FAKE, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES INDEPENDENT BITCHES, THAT PART ♪
♪ I JUST WANT THE PAPER, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES FLAVORED ♪
♪ THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART ♪
♪ OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY! (THAT PART) ♪
♪ BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS, BITCH THIS AIN'T CHIPOTLE ♪
♪ NIGGA WITH AN ATTITUDE, I FEEL LIKE O'SHEA ♪
♪ WALKIN', LIVIN' LEGEND, MAN I FEEL LIKE KOBE ♪
♪ I JUST LEFT THE STRIP CLUB, GOT SOME GLITTER ON ME ♪
♪ WIFEY GONNA KILL ME, SHE THE FEMALE OJ ♪
♪ Y'ALL DON'T FEEL ME, MAN THIS AIN'T OKAY ♪
♪ FOUR SEASONS, TAKE A SHOWER, NEW CLOTHES, I'M RELOADED ♪
♪ EHH RICH NIGGA, STILL EATIN' CATFISH ♪
♪ THAT BITCH AIN'T REALLY BAD, THAT'S A CATFISH ♪
♪ IF I WALK UP OUT OF SAKS FIFTH ♪
♪ HAVE THE PAPARAZZI DOIN' BACKFLIPS ♪
♪ IF I LAY YOU DOWN ON THE MATTRESS ♪
♪ BLOW THE BACK OUT 'TIL YOU BACKLESS ♪
♪ THICK, WE ALREADY ESTABLISHED ♪
♪ SHE JUST GOT 'EM DONE, BRA-STRAPLESS ♪
♪ OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY! (THAT PART) ♪
♪ BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS, BITCH THIS AIN'T CHIPOTLE ♪
♪ (THAT PART) ♪
♪ NIGGA WITH AN ATTITUDE, I FEEL LIKE O'SHEA (THAT PART) ♪
♪ WALKIN', LIVIN' LEGEND, MAN I FEEL LIKE KOBE (THAT PART) ♪
♪ ME NO CONVERSATE WITH THE FAKE, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES INDEPENDENT BITCHES, THAT PART ♪
♪ I JUST WANT THE PAPER, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES FLAVORED ♪
♪ THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART ♪
♪ AYY! THAT PART ♪
♪ BANG THIS SHIT IN THE HOOD ONE TIME ♪
♪ LIL BITCH I'M BACK AND POPPIN' ♪
♪ TELL THAT UGLY BITCH TO MOVE AWAY, I NEED MORE OPTIONS ♪
♪ BROKE? THEN FIX YOUR POCKETS, ALL I DO IS PROFIT ♪
♪ FEW MILLION MADE AND STILL AIN'T CHANGED... THAT PART ♪
♪ ME, MY GIRL GOT MATCHIN' BLING... THAT PART ♪
♪ I'MA GET SO BLOWED, I'MA LOSE MY BRAIN... THAT PART ♪
♪ ME AND XO ONLY THING GO STRAIGHT ♪
♪ NEED ME A BITCH THAT'LL GO BOTH WAYS ♪
♪ STYLE ON TOP OF STYLE, NIGGA ♪
♪ SINCE A YOUNGIN' I WANTED TO BALL, NIGGA ♪
♪ HAD A PISTOL IN MY DRAWLS, NIGGA ♪
♪ WHEN I WAS BROKE, I HAD THE SAUCE, NIGGA ♪
♪ GOT A CHEVY WITH SIDE TO SIDE ON IT ♪
♪ HUNDRED SPOKES, THE DANG-D-DANGS ON IT ♪
♪ GOT A CHOPPER THAT STAND THE FIRE TOO ♪
♪ I PUT YOUR UZI DOWN BESIDE YOU ♪
♪ ME NO CONVERSATE WITH THE FAKE, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES INDEPENDENT BITCHES, THAT PART ♪
♪ I JUST WANT THE PAPER, THAT PART ♪
♪ ALL MY BITCHES FLAVORED ♪
♪ THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART, THAT PART ♪
♪ AYY! THAT PART ♪
♪ THAT PART ♪
♪ WALKIN' LIVIN' LEGEND, MAN I FEEL LIKE KOBE (THAT PART) ♪
♪ I JUST DROPPED 60, MAN I FEEL LIKE KOBE ♪
♪ LAMAR WAS WITH ME, MAN I FEEL LIKE KOBE ♪
♪ PIPPEN AT MY WEDDIN', MAN I FEEL LIKE JORDAN ♪
♪ TRIPPIN' AT MY WEDDIN', I BE RUNNIN' AWAY ♪
♪ AIN'T SAY SHIT, NIGGA ♪
♪ YOU WAS LISTENIN' CLOSE THOUGH ♪
♪ YOU WAS LISTENIN' TO HOES THOUGH ♪
♪ YOU WOULDN'T LISTEN TO THE FLOW THOUGH ♪
♪ LISTEN TO THE 'GOAT ♪
♪ LISTEN TO A YOUNG NIGGA FROM THE 'GO THOUGH ♪
♪ I'MA FREESTYLE THIS MOTHAFUCKA, WHO KNEW? ♪
♪ WHEN I'M WITH MY NIGGAS, NIGGA, SCHOOLBOY Q ♪
♪ AND UH, TOP DAWG, CALL TOP DAWG ♪
♪ GET THAT NIGGA ON THE PHONE ♪
♪ TOP DAWG ON THE PHONE! ♪
♪ AYY, AYY, AYY, AYY, AYY, AYY, AYY! HAH! ♪